Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy will explain how Skooler AS (“Skooler”) uses the personal data we collect from you when you use the mConnect (this website) and related Moodle apps for Teams tabs and channels.

#### WHAT DATA DO WE COLLECT?

Skooler collects the following data:

* Personal identification information (name, email address, phone number, preferred language)
* Company details (name, domains, email address, phone number, preferred language)

#### HOW DO WE COLLECT YOUR DATA?

In the first step, Skooler receive your data as you log in. These details are collected right after the login consent prompted by Microsoft Office 365 Sign-in.

If you decide to start onboading and sumbitting your data, you directly provide Skooler with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when a global administrator enter the details about your location and educational setup.

#### HOW WILL WE USE YOUR DATA?

Skooler collects your data so that we can:

* Contact you about your interest in mConnect
* Setup your mConnect and manage your account
* Email you if important information or actions to your mConnect is needed

#### HOW DO WE STORE YOUR DATA?

Skooler securely stores your data in a database in our data center located in the Microsoft Azure cloud service.

* Before onboarding, Skooler will keep your details for 21 days or until you opt to delete your details
* After onboarding, Skooler will keep your details until the end of service, or until removed or changed by you

Once either of these occurs, we will delete your data by removing your details from our database.

#### CONSENT

**How do you get my consent?**

When logging in the first time, Microsoft Office 365 Sign-in will prompt you to consent that you allow logging in to mConnect with your organization user.

**How do I withdraw my consent?**

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [helpdesk@skooler.com](mailto:helpdesk@skooler.com).

#### COOKIES

**What are cookies?**

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the sites functionality.

For more general information on cookies, visit allaboutcookies.org or see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies.

**How do we use cookies?**

In the mConnect, Skooler uses cookies only in the matter of keeping you signed in.

**Disabling cookies**

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. By disabling cookies, you will no longer be able to stay logged in to mConnect, and the service will not be available for you, or in best case not work as intended.

**Third party cookies**

There are no third party cookies involved in mConnect at this point.

**Privacy policies of other websites**

The mConnect website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy applies only to the mConnect, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.

**More Information**

Hopefully that has clarified things for you and as was previously mentioned if there is something that you aren't sure whether you need or not it's usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site. However if you are still looking for more information then you can contact us through one of our preferred contact methods.

#### DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our [Terms of Use](https://mconnect.skooler.com/tou).

#### THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

mConnect is primarly a service the shows details from your Moodle installation. Skooler is not reliable for any data stored by Moodle.

#### SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

All http channels are secured with https.

Only trusted personnel has access to the services within the Microsoft Azure data center.

#### CANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Skooler keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this website. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

#### QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions about Skooler’s privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Email us for information at: [post@skooler.com](mailto:post@skooler.com)  
Email our support team at: [helpdesk@skooler.com](mailto:helpdesk@skooler.com)  
Call us (Norway): [+47 91589100](tel:+4791589100)  
Call us (International): [425 628 5000](tel:4256285000)

_Last Updated: April 1st, 2020_
